springblowout.com 2013-04-01

# Spring Blowout - Privacy

## Privacy Policy 

I am committed to keeping all your personal details safe and secure. My privacy policy strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**

I am committed to protecting your privacy. I will only use the information that I collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). I will not pass on your details to any third party and do not send out marketing e-mails to customers unless they have registered to receive such material, purchased from me, or downloaded one of my free or paid products.

**The type of information I ‘may’ collect about you includes:**

Your full name  
Your e-mail address  
Your postal address

Generally, this information is requested when you are either downloading free products, when you purchase any of my products (eBooks, software etc.), or when you subscribe to my newsletters. I will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information I hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that I hold about you by e-mailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

**How I Control Your Personal Information**

I will not use your personal information for any other reason other than to contact you. We do not sell, give away or rent your email address to any third party. If in the future I did for any reason wish to rent, sell or use your email address for any other purpose we will ask you for your permission first.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

Your personal information is used for four main purposes and they are as follows:

1\. To send out information, recommendations and resources to you.

2\. To provide assistance to you after you have purchased products from me.

3\. To help me create and deliver content most relevant to you.

4\. To enlighten you about new products, services, tool, upgrades, special offers and information which I feel may be of use to you.

I will only disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on 'Master Resell Rights eBook Firesale'

(b) Protect and defend the rights or property of 'Master Resell Rights eBook Firesale';

(c) Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of 'Master Resell Rights eBook Firesale'.

Back To Main Page

The Publisher has strived to be as accurate and complete as possible in the creation of this report, notwithstanding the fact that he does not warrant or represent at any time that the contents within are accurate due to the rapidly changing nature of the Internet. While all attempts have been made to verify information provided in this publication, the Publisher assumes no responsibility for errors, omissions, or contrary interpretation of the subject matter herein. Any perceived slights of specific persons, peoples, or organizations are unintentional. In practical advice books, like anything else in life, there are no guarantees of income made. Readers are cautioned to reply on their own judgment about their individual circumstances to act accordingly. This book is not intended for use as a source of legal, business, accounting or financial advice. All readers are advised to seek services of competent professionals in legal, business, accounting and finance fields. ClickBank is a registered trademark of Keynetics Inc., a Delaware corporation. ResellRightsMachine.com is not affiliated with Keynetics Inc. or Google Inc. in any way, nor does Keynetics Inc. or Google Inc. sponsor or approve any ResellRightsMachine.com product. Keynetics Inc. expresses no opinion as to the correctness of any of the statements made by this site in the materials on ResellRightsMachine.com Web page.
